have you felt sad recently over time
I've learned to take the feeling as it
comes accepting it like a wave rising
and falling there isn't always a
solution as for me I find comfort in
nature and in spraying my spirit
particularly yearns for flowers blue
flax blooms just outside my front door
and it is one of my favorite flowers of
the season one day when I needed to
raise my spirits
I picked a bouquet to bring home so to
inspire my creativity
[Music]
you
yeah just like that I felt better
my soul arrested my mind at peace we are
living in such a crazy time right now
and I know it is very upsetting and very
difficult for so many people myself
included
there are times this year that I have
found myself worrying about the future
and for humankind and is always worrying
about the planet sometimes it becomes
too much to bear and I find that that is
the most important time to go outside
and take a walk it's something so simple
and yet I find again and again that it's
the answer I need you have no control
over the actions of others and I think
that is the root of a lot of the anger
that people feel right now I've accepted
that I cannot control the spirit of
someone else
however every time that I feel
frustrated about the actions of others I
know that the one thing that I can
control is my own spirit and that I have
complete control over that and that is
liberating I think it's also such an
important message for everyone to hear
that you have at anytime of the
potential to become someone you are
proud of someone who is kind and
courageous someone who is compassionate
we can become that person I wasn't
always the person that I most admired
and now I am and I'm very proud to say
that I'll tell you one thought that I
found really comforting and it is if at
the end of your journey your life
journey all you can say that you have
achieved is a life that has been lived
by kindness and compassion then you have
lived one of the best lives of all time
thank you guys so much for watching this
video my intention was not to make a sad
video and I hope it is not sad to you my
intent
Jim was to share a little bit of the
words that I say to myself that make me
continue feeling hopeful and fighting
despair so thank you all